I have a fingerprint sensor in my phone. It has a 6
megapixel camera but an on-screen
fingerprint sensor. Brother, what do you have? It
started on the A and it broke. I only have a home.
Hey, you can take insurance for
yourself and all your customers
because I am a group insurance
policy for all my prime numbers from
ICICI Lombard. It covers
your health. Good songs Amitabh
Bachchan and liquid damages too.
If due to any accidental accident, your hand
skin breaks and stops working or gets
damaged due to water spillage, then there is no need
to worry. You
can easily enter the details and share the number. Your
phone will be taken from your home, repaired and
returned safely. We claim that
you will not find cheaper handset insurance than this. The
insurance
is invalid for irregular use of your phone such as improper
handling i.e. holding the phone in the wrong way or going out to
play with it. Excessive
carelessness i.e.
taking the phone to the bathroom etc.
Intentional damage to the phone for 10 minutes i.e.
intentional damage to the phone. This insurance is for
Cosmic Dancer.
Also invalid on Distance Crunches and all other phone apps series
Terms and conditions apply, notable among which is that
Insurance will be provided only on purchase of new phone on the same day
Plan will
commence only after payment of full fee Customer has to
comply with the plan terms Customer
details should match with their valid Government ID Customer should be
above 18 years of age and should be an
Indian citizen
Insurance should not be registered from outside India
Update your details immediately on purchase of new phone Claim should be
lodged within 48 hours of receipt
with nominal charges In case of any
issue regarding this claim, you have to directly
contact ICICI Lombard
I am Shivkant, I am travelling by train from any